Canyon Cinema Records, ca. 1961-2009 M1681
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2. Filmmakers
  - Vanderbeek, Stan (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Varela, Willie (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Verstappen, Harrie (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Wallin, Michael (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Walsh, Jack (Box 29, Folder 11)
    File includes computer disk
  - Watkins, Peter (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Watkins, Peter (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Weisman, Phil (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Wellington, Fred (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Welsby, Chris (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Wendt, Doug (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - White, Chel (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - White, Jac (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Wieland, Joyce (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Wilchusky, Le Ann Bartok (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Wiley, Dorothy (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Wilkins, Timoleon (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Wilson, Mark (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Wood, Bruce (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Wright, Charles (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Yalkut, Jud (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Zdravic, Andrej (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Bartlett, Scott (Oversize-box 48, Folder 2)
  - Abrahams-Wilson, Andy (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - About Men Workshop (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Adams, Dan (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Adams, Russell R. (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Adelphia Pictures Corporation (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Adrian, Marc (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Alberts, Ulvis (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Allan, Bill & Bruce Nauman (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Alperin, Leslie (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Amar, Maurice (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Anderson, Karl (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Andreae, Sypko & Drury Pifer (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Arlyck, Ralph (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Arnold, Steve (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Ascher, Robert (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Attanasio, Robert (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Avidan, David (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Bacilla, Emil (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Bailey, Dan (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Bain, Claire (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Bak, Gamma (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Baker, Will (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Baldewicz, Bill (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Ballis, George (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Baldwin, Christie (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Banks, Barbara (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Barber, Victor (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Barens, Edgar A. (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Barnes, R.G. (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Barrish, Jerry (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Baross, Jan (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Bartell, Shirley (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Bartlett, Freude (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Bass, Howard (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Bass, Warren (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Bates, Al (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Batra, Jagdish (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Beamer, Charles (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Beauvais, Yann (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Bechard, Gorman (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Beck, Stephen (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - Beckjord, Jon (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Beeler, Kathleen (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - Beerger, Norman (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - Bell, Forest (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - Bell, Geoffrey (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Bellocchio, Marco (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Bennett, Dave (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Berg, Lars (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Betancourt, Michael (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Betts, Larry (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Beveridge, Richard (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Bezdechi, Adrien (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Birmelin, Bruce (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Blackman, Gary (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Blair, Wendy (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Blaskovitch, Tim (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Bloch, Howard (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Blosser, Will (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Boatwright, David (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Bode, Boris (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Bokanowski, Patrick (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Bolster, Larry E. (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Bosustow, Tee (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Bowles, Philip (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Breer, Emily (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Brener, Tom (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Brick, Richard (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Bridgers/Musiek, Lee (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Brilliant, Barry (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Brown, Adele (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Brown, Robert J. & Frank Olvey (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Brynntrup, Michael (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Buchbinder, Amnon (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Buehler, David (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Bundy, Peter (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Cambou, Don (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Camper, Fred (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Cantow, Roberta (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Cantrill, Arthur & Corinne (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Cariati, Edwin (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Carnot, Sylvie (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Carolfi, Jerome (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Carson, Kit (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Cato, Don (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Caveglia, Jerry (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - Cerveris, Don & Kelly Hart (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - Chamberlain, Bob (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - Ciesielka, Thomas (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - Cinemalab (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - Chao, Tom (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Chappell, Walter (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Cheng, Fuding (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Citron, Robert (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Clark, Jim (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Clarke, R.G. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Cockrell, Suzanne (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Cohen, Karl (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Colburn, Martha (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Coleman, Jeremy (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Colmer, Roy (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Colt, Clay (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Cook, Jerome T. (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Cowan, Bob (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Craig, Ray (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Crawford, Neelon (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Creson, Steve (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Csicsery, George & Jerry Anderson (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Cummins, Phil C. (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Cutaia, John (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Daley, Sandy (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Danielson, Rob (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Darbonne, Rodger (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Davis, Dave (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Davis, Mark & Connacht (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - De Bruyn, Dirk (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Deitch, Donna (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Delabre, Patrick (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - DeLuise, Michael (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Denny, Glen (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - DeRoux, Ken (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Derry, Charles (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - DeVault, James (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Devensky, David (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Dews, David (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Diamant, Ralph (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Dixon, Wheeler (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - Dobson, Jane (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - Cleve, Bastian (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Doing, Karel (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Donahue, Patrick (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Dorius, Lynn (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Douglas, Jim (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Drori, Thalia (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Dvorak, Robert Regis (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Dundas, Edd (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Eagle, Arnold (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Eagle, Steve (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Earthworm Films (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Ebersole, Medora (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Elam, JoAnn (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Ellis, Craig (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Ellis, Leonard (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Elman, Lynne (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - El Teatro Campesino (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Emrich, Bob (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - English, Ed (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - English, William (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Epp, Ellie (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Evans, Jane (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Evans, Jay (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Fabricant, Ira (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Fairfax, Susanne (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Farber, Eric (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Feltzer, Susan Jane (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Fenz, Robert (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Filippo, Mary (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Fillinger, Paul (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Finne, Ron (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Finne, Ron (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Fisher, Holly (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - Fisher, Morgan (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - Floyd, Carl (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Flying Haystacks (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Focus Pocus Film Squad (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - Fong, Robert (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - Ford, Phillip (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - Forney, Darrell (Box 57, Folder 40)
  - Forrer, Paul (Box 57, Folder 41)
  - Fort, Deborah (Box 57, Folder 42)
  - Foss, Janet (Box 57, Folder 43)
  - Francia, Henry (Box 57, Folder 44)
  - Francis, Rell G. (Box 57, Folder 45)
  - Frankel, Zygmunt (Box 57, Folder 46)
  - Frazier, Harry (Box 57, Folder 47)
  - Fridge, Roy (Box 57, Folder 48)
  - Frishman, Gil (Box 57, Folder 49)
  - Frost, Jacqueline (Box 57, Folder 50)
  - Frye, Brian (Box 57, Folder 51)
  - Fujuii, Seiichi (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Dewdney, A. Keewatin (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Feldman, Robert (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Gaikowski, Richard (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Gale, Kira (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Gee, Daven (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Gentile, Jennifer (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Gershfield, Burton G. (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Gerson, Barry (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Gerstein, David (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Giammona, Sal (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Gibsone, Julian (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Gietzen, Gordon (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Gilberti, Nina (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Giorgio, Bob (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Giritlian, Virginia (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Giuliano, Tom (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Goldman, Martin (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Goodman, Mark (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Gordon, Bette (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Gorg, Alan (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Gorski, Nicholas (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Graham, Daniel (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Greenberg, Bob (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Gregory, David V. (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Gruben, Patricia (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Gruenberger, John (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Grunberg, Laurie (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Guerrero, Eduardo (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Guillet, Guy (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Gullifer, Jason (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Guttenplan, Howard (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Guzaitis, Joseph (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Haertling, Joel (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Hafford, Patrick (Box 58, Folder 35)
    contains photographs
  - Hallinger, David (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Halper, Robert (Box 58, Folder 37)
  - Halpern, Amy (Box 58, Folder 38)
  - Halprin, Anna (Box 58, Folder 39)
  - Hardy, Varda (Box 58, Folder 40)
  - Harkness, Richard (Box 58, Folder 41)
  - Harlot, Scarlot (Box 58, Folder 42)
  - Harrar, Jamie (Box 58, Folder 43)
  - Harrison, David III (Box 58, Folder 44)
  - Harvey, Stephanie (Box 58, Folder 45)
  - Haslanger, Martha (Box 58, Folder 46)
  - Haugse, John E. & Bill (Box 58, Folder 47)
  - Haxton, David (Box 58, Folder 48)
  - Hayes, Rory (Box 58, Folder 49)
  - Hayeem, Ben (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Heilemann, Paul (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Heinz, Jerry (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Hella, Patrick (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Hellman, Kit (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Helm, Nan (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Henderson, Mike (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Herman, Todd (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Hernandez, Al (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Heyl, Kurt (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Hill, Charlotte (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Hill, Seth (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Hock, Louis (Oversize-box 49, Folder 5)
  - Hoffman, George (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Holden, David (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Hollensen, Peter (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Hollins, Michael (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Hoolboom, Mike (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Hopper, Philip (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Horvath, Karl (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Huckabee, Tom & Will van Overbeek (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Hughes, Donald (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Hunt, John (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Hunter, Kirk (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Huppert, Erwin (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Hurwitz, Elise (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Huston, Larry (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Heinz, John (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Idemitsu, Mako (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Irvine, Charles L. (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Janetzko, Christoph (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Janetzko, Christoph (Box 59, Folder 31)
  - Jenkins, Patrick (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - Jesionka, Henry (Box 59, Folder 33)
  - Johnson, Flip (Box 59, Folder 34)
  - Johnson, Karen (Box 59, Folder 35)
  - Jones, Ed (Box 59, Folder 36)
  - Jordan-Bastow, Gretchen (Box 59, Folder 37)
  - Jost, Jon (Box 59, Folder 38)
  - Kabak, Stephen (Box 59, Folder 39)
  - Kanar, Dick (Box 59, Folder 40)
  - Katzke, M.R. (Box 59, Folder 41)
  - Keene, William (Box 59, Folder 42)
  - Kelly, Dexter (Box 59, Folder 43)
  - Kendal, Nancy (Box 59, Folder 44)
  - Kennedy, Shelby (Box 59, Folder 45)
  - Kent, Clark (Box 59, Folder 46)
  - Kerr, Richard (Box 59, Folder 47)
  - Kerr, Richard (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Killelea, Anne (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Kirby, Aurora (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Kirch, John (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Kirk-O-Matic (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Kish, Anne (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Kiyooka, Fumiko (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Klein, Michael (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Kleinhans, Chuck (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Kling, George (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Klockseim, Steve (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Knoop, John (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Kobashigawa, Jun (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Koppy, Michael (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Korschil, Thomas (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Kortz, Dirk (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Kosower, Herbert (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Krausie, C.E. (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Krigbaum/Diokno/Kyriazi (Box 60, Folder 19)
    aka KDK Films
  - Krumins, Daina (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Kuchar, Mike (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Kuchar, Mike (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Kull, Dennis R. (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Lair, Richard (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Lambert, Lothar (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Lane, Bradley (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Latham, John (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Laughlin, Kathleen (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Lawrence, Paul (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Lawrence, Peter (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Le Bruyn, David (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Lefort, Lou (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - Legge, Michael (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - Leggett, Mike (Box 60, Folder 34)
  - Leggo, Christopher (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - Leimbacher, Irina (Box 60, Folder 36)
  - Lemaitre, Maurice (Box 60, Folder 37)
  - Leonardi, Alfredo (Box 60, Folder 38)
  - Lerman, Richard (Box 60, Folder 39)
    includes photographs
  - Lesage, Julia (Box 60, Folder 40)
  - Lester, Howard (Box 60, Folder 41)
  - Levy, Lenny (Box 60, Folder 42)
  - Levy, Maurice (Box 60, Folder 43)
  - Lewin, Jeff (Box 60, Folder 44)
  - Lewis, Laurie (Box 60, Folder 45)
  - Lewis, Laurie (Box 60, Folder 46)
    aka Lawrence Lewis
  - L'Heureaux, Albert (Box 60, Folder 47)
  - Lions, Michael (Box 60, Folder 48)
  - Lipskis, Peter (Box 60, Folder 49)
  - Lloyd, Don (Box 60, Folder 50)
  - Loeser, Doris (Box 60, Folder 51)
  - Lohmann, Karl (Box 60, Folder 52)
  - Lowe, Pelle (Box 60, Folder 53)
  - Lundahl, Paul (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Lyman, Charles (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Lyon, Danny (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Mahler, Al (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Malone, Sean (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Mann, Ron (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Margulies, Laura (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Marin, Eric (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Marin, Lorne (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Marioni, Paul (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Martin, Katrina (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Mattox, Janis (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Maziere, Michael (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - McAdams, Heather (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - McCandless, Peter (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - McDougall, Marina (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - McGowan, Bruce (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - McGowan, Mark (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - McLaughlin, Dan (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - McLaughlin, Dave (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - McLuskie, Carolyn (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - McNeil, David (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Mead, Wrik (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Meader, Abbott (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Mekas, Adolphas (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Menefee, Emory (Box 61, Folder 26)
    includes photograph
  - Merciez, Richard G. (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Meter, Barbara (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Metzgar, Eric (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Meyers, Harvey (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Michalak, David (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - Michaud, Hans (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Miller, Scott (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - Milligan, John & Victor Moscoso (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Milton, Jack (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - Misfud, Robert (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Mobia, Steve (Box 61, Folder 37)
  - Montfaucon Research Center (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - Montgomery, Edward (Box 61, Folder 39)
  - Moore, Michael (Box 61, Folder 40)
  - Moreno, Ralph (Box 61, Folder 41)
  - Morgan, Hilary (Box 61, Folder 42)
  - Moritz, William (Box 61, Folder 43)
  - Morris Productions (Box 61, Folder 44)
  - Morton, Geer (Box 61, Folder 45)
  - Moyer, Larry (Box 61, Folder 46)
  - Mueller, Jerry (Box 61, Folder 47)
  - Mukamal, Alan E.L. (Box 61, Folder 48)
  - Mullen, Michael (Box 61, Folder 49)
  - Nameth, Ronald (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Nameth, Ronald (Box 62, Folder 2)
    contains printing materials
  - Nanney, David (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Nathanson, Linda (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Neidhardt, Jim (Box 62, Folder 5)
    contains photographic negative
  - Nekes, Werner (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Nekes, Werner (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Nekes, Werner (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Nervig, Sandra L. (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Nolan, Roy (Box 62, Folder 10)
    contains artwork
  - Noren, Andrew (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Novak, Franklyn (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Oberhaus, Patricia (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Obern, G. Vaughan (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - O'Brien, Jerry (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Okun, Jenny (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Olson, Ralph (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Ort, Myron (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Osborn, Steve (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Ostrovsky, Vivian (Box 62, Folder 20)
    contains photographs and press materials
  - O'Toole, Owen (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Overland Vegetable Stagecoach (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Paggie, Michael J. (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Palomino, Ernie (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Parent, Bob (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - de la Parra, Pim (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Parker, Alice Anne (Box 63, Folder 2)
    aka Anne Severson
  - Parker, Alice Anne (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Peil, Jerrold (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Perkins, Steve (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Perlberg, Janet (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Perry, Dave E. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Perz, Dan (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Petrochuk, Kon (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Petrochuk, Kon (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Phillpott, Richard (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Pollack, Barry (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Ponger, Lisl (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Portillo, Lourdes (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Priestly, Joanna (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Pritza, Michael (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Quinn, Mike (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Quinnell, Ken (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Rafferty, Kevin (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Ramby, Craig (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Ramsing, Roy (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Ramsing, Pam (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Random, Derrell (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Rayher, Robert (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Razutis, Al (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Razutis, Al (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Razutis, Al (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Read, Aggy (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Reamer, Keith L. (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Reckord, Lloyd (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Redgreen, Karen (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Reed, Larry (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Rehblock, Loren (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Reichline, Neil (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Reinders, Kristie (Box 63, Folder 35)
    contains computer media
  - Renan, Sheldon (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Re/Search Publications (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - Revaux, Anthony (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Reynolds, John (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Rhee, Ye Sook (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - Rhoads, Tom (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Rice, Ray (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Ringo, David (Box 63, Folder 43)
  - Robbin, Lawrence (Box 63, Folder 44)
  - Robinson, Jonathan (Box 63, Folder 45)
  - Rodan, Keith (Box 63, Folder 46)
    contains original artwork
  - Rodriguez, Reymon (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Roll, Henry (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Rose, Lisa (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Rosen, Hesh (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Rosette, Jason (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Ross, Allen (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Ross, Rock (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Roth, Phillip B. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Rouda, Saul (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Rubin, Jon (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Rudnick, Michael (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Ryan, Paul (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Sabo, John (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Sadan, Mark (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Sadier, Sim (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Safran, Fred (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Saks, Eric (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Salmore, Charles (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Salvo, Calgero (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Sanborn, Keith (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Sander, Louis (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Sandman, Virginia (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Sands, Ilene (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Savage, Rob (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Savage-Lee, Caroline (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Sax, Erin (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Schaaf, Allen (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Schaaf, Russell (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Scheller, Tom & Jerry (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Schiappacasse, Robert (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Schiffner, Gregg (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Schlemowitz, Joel (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - Schneider, Ira (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - Schoenfeld, Claire & Mark Freeman (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - Schulz, Ingrid (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - Schwartz, Gary (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - Sears, Loren (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - Sears, Loren (Box 64, Folder 38)
  - See, Richard (Box 64, Folder 39)
  - Seibert, Erich (Box 64, Folder 40)
  - Semsel, George (Box 64, Folder 41)
  - Serke, Udo (Box 64, Folder 42)
  - Seve, Robert (Box 64, Folder 43)
  - SF Newsreel (Box 64, Folder 44)
  - Shah, Krishna (Box 64, Folder 45)
  - Shapiro, Steven G. (Box 64, Folder 46)
  - Sheil-Kama Productions (Box 64, Folder 47)
  - Sherman, Stuart (Box 64, Folder 48)
  - Sherrill, Don (Box 64, Folder 49)
  - Sideshow Cinema (Box 64, Folder 50)
  - Siegel, David (Box 64, Folder 51)
  - Siegel, Steve (Box 64, Folder 52)
  - Simondet, Lee (Box 64, Folder 53)
  - Simons, Frank (Box 64, Folder 54)
  - Simons, John (Box 64, Folder 55)
  - Simpson, David (Box 64, Folder 56)
  - Sinden, Tony (Box 64, Folder 57)
  - Singer, Joel (Box 64, Folder 58)
  - Sive, Gene (Box 64, Folder 59)
  - Schmoeller, David (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Sloan, Tai (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Sloat, Commodore (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Slon, Jonathan (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Snider, Dean (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Soltero, Jose (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Sommer, Ines (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Sondheim, Alan (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Sondheim, Alan (Box 65, Folder 9)
    includes a copy of Sondheim's "Disorders of the Real"
  - Stanton, Richard (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Starkman, Marvin (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Sternberg, Barbara (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Sternberg, Barbara (Box 65, Folder 13)
    contains photographs and computer media
  - Szirtes, Andras (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Wild, Don (Box 65, Folder 15)
    aka III Films
  - Yeo, Rob (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - B.Y.M. Productions (Box 65, Folder 17)
    aka P.D. Spoecker
  - Ball, Gordon (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Poetry Film Workshop (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Baillie, Bruce: Correspondence, 1998 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    one postcard
  - De Valois, Geoffrey (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Palazzolo, Tom (Box 77, Folder 2)
    postcard to Dominic Angerame
  - Shepard, Tim (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Sterne, Mark (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Steward, Kenneth (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Stewart, Michael (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Stiglitz, Zack (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Stone, Dave (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Stookey, Jeff (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Strombeck, Grant (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Stubblefield, Laurisa (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Sullivan, Terry (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Sunier, John (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Sweeny, Moira (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Symanski, Don (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Szirtes, Andras (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Tadic, Linda (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Tartaglia, Jerry (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Tatano, Alfonso (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Taylor, Edward S. (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Taylor, Ron (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Telley, Ramzy (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Tellez, German & Christine Piotter (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Terranella, Fran Burst (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Theise, E.S. (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Thomas, John (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Thomas, R.J. (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Thompson, W.C. (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Thoms, Albie (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - Thurber, Robert (Box 77, Folder 30)
  - Torbet, Bruce (Box 77, Folder 31)
  - Toronto, Richard/End of the World Productions (Box 77, Folder 32)
  - Torrossian, Garine (Box 77, Folder 33)
  - Tougas, Kirk (Box 77, Folder 34)
  - Triman, Tom (Box 77, Folder 35)
  - Turano, Paul (Box 77, Folder 36)
  - Tynan, Dermot (Box 77, Folder 37)
  - Ursin, Nikolai (Box 77, Folder 38)
  - Valentine, Kenneth (Box 77, Folder 39)
  - Van Meter, Ben (Box 77, Folder 40)
    contains photographs and mounted photo-collages
  - Vasquez, Angel (Box 77, Folder 41)
  - Verstappen, Harrie (Box 77, Folder 42)